var questionBank =
[
  {
    question: "The last daily Calvin and Hobbes comic strip ran on December 31, 1995.",
    answers: ["True", "False", "No one knows"],
    correct: "True"
  },
  {
    question: "Calvin and Hobbes are named after these two great thinkers:",
    answers: ["John Calvin, Thomas Hobbes", "Francis Calvin, John Hobbes", "Sebastian Calvin, Harold Hobbes"],
    correct: "John Calvin, Thomas Hobbes"
  },
  {
    question: "What are the names of Calvin's parents",
    answers: ["Marvin and Molly", "Never Revealed", "Jack and Jill"],
    correct: "Never Revealed"
  },
  {
    question: "How does Hobbes get clean?",
    answers: ["Bath", "Hose", "Washing Machine"],
    correct: "Washing Machine"
  },
  {
    question: "Spaceman Spiff has carried all these weapons EXCEPT:",
    answers: ["Atomic Napalm Neutralizer", "Spiffoon", "Death Ray Blaster"],
    correct: "Spiffoon"
  },
  {
    question: "Calvin and Hobbes get scared when one of these creations springs to life and begins multiplying:",
    answers: ["Leftover Salad", "Snowman", "Scarecrow"],
    correct: "Snowman"
  },
  {
    question: "Who's the little girl who lives next door to Calvin?",
    answers: ["Susie Derkins", "Sally Weaver", "Jane Jenson"],
    correct: "Susie Derkins"
  },
  {
    question: "What is the name of the game that Calvin and Hobbes play, in which the only rule is that they can never play by the same rules twice?",
    answers: ["Hobbesball", "Croquet", "Calvinball"],
    correct: "Calvinball"
  },
  {
    question: "Calvin and Hobbes' secret club is called:",
    answers: ["B.O.O.G.E.R.", "N.A.T.O.", "G.R.O.S.S."],
    correct: "G.R.O.S.S."
  },
  {
    question: "Who wrote Calvin and Hobbes?",
    answers: ["Bill Watterson", "Calvin Kline", "Bill Amend"],
    correct: "Bill Watterson"
  },
  {
    question: "What inexpensive item was used by Calvin and Hobbes as a Transmogrifier, Flying Time Machine, and Duplicator?",
    answers: ["Cardboard Box", "Toothbrush", "None of the above"],
    correct: "Cardboard Box"
  },
  {
    question: "What was the name of the bully who sometimes beat up Calvin and took his lunch money?",
    answers: ["George", "Moe", "Nelson"],
    correct: "Moe"
  },
]